Anyelo Petit

Phone: H: +58 269 2201782, M: +58 414 3639602

Email: anyelopetit@gmail.com

Address: Acueducto Street 59th, Caja de Agua, Punto Fijo 4102, Falcón State, Venezuela

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anyelo-petit/

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced Ruby on Rails developer who is enthusiastic about writing clean, efficient, and accessible code in a functional framework. Committed to the total development lifecycle, the maintenance of code quality and bug-free applications is of the utmost importance. Expert in leveraging the latest software tools to optimize data storage, e-commerce functionality, and fluidity across mobile platforms. A leader in identifying opportunities for applications development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Experienced Ruby on Rails developer with competencies in Jquery, and Ajax.
- Knowledgeable and certified in JavaScript.
- Familiar with the automation of testing platforms.
- Able to integrate several databases together to form one database system.
- Masterful with UI styling tool Bootstrap and the Sass CSS preprocessor.
- Clean code writer that is fully versed in object-oriented coding.
- Committed to scalable design and function as well as seamless integration.
- Competent with templating languages on the server side such as Slim and Haml.
- Creative with database construction to best support application monetization.
- Agile experience using Git versions control for creation and manipulation of code repositories, team work and the management of code histories for a safe and stable development environment.

EMPLOYMENT:

Slice Group (January 2018 - Present)

Back-End Coordinator and Ruby on Rails Developer

- Leadership for a team of approximately nine 9+ Ruby, Python and PHP developers.
- Control of process and monitoring production of Back-End development department.
- Planning projects and creating new projects ideas.

Slice Group (June 2017 - January 2018) Junior Ruby on Rails Developer

• Creation and functional development of web platforms and applications.

• Quickly development using Agile UX and SCRUM methodology.

Slice Group (September 2016 - June 2017)

Front-End Developer

- Designing and preparing detailed web structures using HTML and CSS with Ruby technology.
- . Measuring designs about web platforms using Responsive Design and UX interfaces.

Slice Group (January 2016 - September 2016) UI/UX Designer

- Preparation, design and planation of UI design for web platforms with comfortable user experience.
- Creation of web wireframes for a future functional development.

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

2014 - 2019: Universidad Nacional Experimental de la Fuerza Armada (*National Experimental University of Armed Force*)

Ordinary Degree in Systems Engineering

Minor subject: Systems Management, Software Development

2008 - 2014: Padre Víctor Iriarte "Fe y Alegría"

Technical Technician in Administration, mention Computer

Minor subject: Computer Maintenance, Administrative Systems

REFERENCES:

Ing. Adriel Pelayo, Quantity Surveyor: +353 83 1710040

Bsc. Angelica Robles, Software Developer: +353 83 1700338

Bsc. Luis Tremont, Sales and Account Executive: +58 412 1231328

Bsc. Carlos Valerio, Graphic Designer: +58 424 6986618